Richard Enlow Human-Centered Design







I'm an experienced product designer (UX, UI, IxD) based in San Francisco. I'm a problem solver by heart and have embedded myself in design and technology for over a decade. I've delivered and lead design efforts across diverse products and industries. I love building useful tools and delightful experiences with kind, smart people.

EXPERIENCE

Dispatch Logistics CEO & Founder AUG 2017 - CURRENT

Pivotal Labs Product Designer & Design Manager DEC 2014 - AUG 2017

Fuze

Principal Product Designer (UX/IxD) SEPT 2013 - DEC 2014

Amoe.ba UX/UI Designer OCT 2012 - SEPT 2013

Web & Graphic Designer 2005 - 2012

EDUCATION

Cont'd Education

2005 - CURRENT

CIT - Web & Graphic Design **GRADUATED 2005**

Our team worked to streamline wholesale distribution, from order entry to delivery. I led user research, product design, product management, and operations, working to power up the supply chain.

As a product designer (IxD, UX, Vis), I helped clients deliver valuable and innovative apps for their business and users. As a design manager, I coached, mentored and grew the Product Design practice.

CLIENTS INCLUDED Mercedes-Benz



As a product designer (IxD, UX, Vis), I helped clients deliver valuable and innovative apps for their business and users. As a design manager, I coached, mentored, and help grow the Product Design practice.

I helped companies build out useful, intuitive products, from rapidprototyping through pixel-perfect implementation. Projects ranged from project management platforms to social networks to non-profit.

CLIENTS INCLUDED **mozilla** C.



change.org 💸



I designed websites, emails, catalogs, advertising across online and print media both in-house and agency-based. See LinkedIn for details.

Courses at Stanford, General Assembly, Nielsen Norman, UCSD, and D. School in Design Thinking, User Research, Lean Startup, Front End Dev, Human Centered Design, & Interaction Design.

Founders Award Recipient, Student Mentor

SKILLS

Seasoned design practitioner - User Experience (UX), Interaction, User Interface (UI), Visual, and Service Design. Experienced in user research methods both qualitative and quantitative. Background in designing for iOS, Android, Apple Watch, Responsive Web, and Desktop applications. An expert facilitator with people and practice management experience. Experienced with modern design tools; Sketch, Invision, Illustrator, etc. and front-end web technologies (HTML, CSS, JS).